distance-calculator.co.uk 2016-03-07

# Privacy and Cookies

### Privacy Policy

**"Distance Calculator" Privacy Policy**  
Privacy is an important concern for internet users, and is something that "Distance Calculator" takes very seriously. What follows is an explanation of "Distance Calculator"'s policy for protecting users' personal information.

"Distance Calculator" keeps the personal information we receive from our Site completely confidential and uses it solely to provide the goods and services you have requested and for internal business review purposes. We will not share your personal information with any other parties without your express consent other than as is necessary to provide the goods and services you have requested or as may be required by law.

**Collection of your Personal Information:** The personal information we collect may include your name and e-mail address and any feedback or comments you have provided to us. We may collect certain information about your visit, such as the browser you use; the date and time you access the Site; the pages that you access while at the Site and the URL of the Internet site from which you have been linked directly to our Site. This information is used to help improve the Site and administer the Site.

**Use of your Personal Information:** The personal information collected on this Site will be used to provide the services you have requested. In addition we may use your personal information to provide you with important information about the product or service that you are using, including new releases updates and notifications. We may also send you information about other "Distance Calculator" products and services.

**Use of cookies  **"Distance Calculator" uses cookies to track usage. For auto login (where applicable) a cookie is sent from our server and is stored on your computer's hard drive.

Cookies are used by "Distance Calculator" to:

a) Enable us to identify you without having to ask you for username and password (if applicable).  
b) Measure usage.  
c) Track movement within the "Distance Calculator" Internet site. 

If you do not wish to accept any of these cookies or wish to be notified when a cookie is sent you can modify your browser preferences. If you refuse to accept the permanent cookie that is saved on your computer's hard drive then you will not be able to use any Auto login facility (if applicable). If you choose not to accept session cookies then you may not be able to use all of the facilities offered on "Distance Calculator". 

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.

  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).)

**What is "Distance Calculator"'s policy on e-mailing?** "Distance Calculator" may contact you from time to time to draw your attention to information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out from receiving such e-mail when giving us your e-mail address, or at any time thereafter by responding to such an e-mail or contacting "Distance Calculator" customer services.

**What will "Distance Calculator" do with my feedback** "Distance Calculator" values your comments and views on the Site and also welcomes information concerning distances. We will use all comments and information you provide to improve the service "Distance Calculator" is able to offer. By submitting feedback and or information concerning an distance you grant "Distance Calculator" a non-exclusive license in perpetuity to use such feedback and or information and to sub-license others to use it.

**Legal responsibilities** "Distance Calculator" reserves the right to disclose personal information if required to do so by law, or in the good faith and belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, respond to claims, or protect the rights, property or safety of "Distance Calculator", employees or members.

**Who should I contact if I have any questions or concerns about my privacy?** If you have any questions or concerns about your privacy and "Distance Calculator" please contact the "Distance Calculator" customer service

**Promotions**

Participation in promotions is subject to our terms and conditions. We "Distance Calculator" reserve the right to cancel without notice any promotion we may operate on this site.

We emploly methods for the detection of gaming of promotions and systems. Where this is identified any points accrued will be forfeited. Our sole determination of this is final.
